University of Houston Statistics
University of Houston Libraries
University of Houston Statistics
1947-1970
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
University of Houston.
16.00 Linear Feet
The U.H. Statistics 1947-1970 contains various reports issued by the university. Some of the topics of these reports include Teacher Load Reports, New Students, Statistics, Coordinating Board Reports, and Grade Distribution Reports.
1969-069
Scope and Contents
The U.H. Statistics 1947-1970 contains various reports issued by the university. Some of the topics of these reports include Teacher Load Reports, New Students, Statistics, Coordinating Board Reports, and Grade Distribution Reports.
Arrangement of Materials
The collection is arranged chronologically with the materials beginning in 1947 and ending in 1970.
Forms part of the University Archives.
Index Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
University of Houston
Genre/Form of Material:
Reports
Access Restrictions
Open for research.
Acquisition
Detailed Description
- Administrative Managment
  A Study of Administrative Managment
  - A Study of Administrative Management - Chapter VI: University Development Activities (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Study of Administrative Management - Volume One (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A Study of Administrative Management - Volume Two (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - University of Houston Teacher Load Reports 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - University of Houston Teacher Load Reports 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - University of Houston Teacher Load Reports 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - University of Houston Teacher Load Reports 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Enrollment Analysis - Book 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - New Students - Book 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Student Roster ALPH, Fall 1954 thru 2nd Summer 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Binders
  - Grade Distribution, 2nd Summer 1954 (Item 4)
  - Statistics, Fall 1955 thru 2nd Summer 1956 (Item 5)
  - Statistics, Fall 1956 thru 2nd Summer 1957 (Item 6)
  - Statistics, Fall 1956 thru 2nd Summer 1957 (Item 7)
  - JCA - Book 1 of 2, 1957 (Item 8)
  - JCA - Book 2 of 2, 1957 (Item 9)
  - Statistics, Fall 1957 thru 2nd Summer 1958 (Item 10)
  - Statistics, Fall 1957 thru 2nd Summer 1958 (Item 11)
  - Cresap, McCormick, and Paget Report, 1959 (Item 12)
  - Statistics, Fall 1958 thru 2nd Summer 1959 (Item 13)
  - Statistics, Fall 1958 thru 2nd Summer 1959 (Item 14)
  - Rank Masters - Campus and Downtown, Fall 1959 (Item 15)
  - Statistics, Fall 1959 thru 2nd Summer 1960 (Item 16)
  - Statistics, Fall 1960 thru 2nd Summer 1961 (Item 17)
  - Schedule Listing - Book 2 (Item 18)
  - Statistics, Fall 1961 thru 2nd Summer 1962 (Item 19)
  - Statistics, Fall 1961 thru 2nd Summer 1962 (Item 20)
  - Statistics, Fall 1962 thru 2nd Summer 1963 (Item 21)
  - Statistics, Fall 1962 thru 2nd Summer 1963 (Item 22)
  - Statistics, Fall 1963 thru 2nd Summer 1964 (Item 23)
  - Statistics, Fall 1964 thru 2nd Summer 1965 (Item 24)
  - Statistics, Fall 1965 (Item 25)
  - Coordinating Board Reports, Spring 1965 - 2nd Summer 1965 (Item 26)
  - Statistics, Spring 1966 (Item 27)
  - Statistical, 1st and 2nd Summer 1966 (Item 28)
  - Statistical, Fall 1966 (Item 29)
  - Coordinating Board Reports, Fall 1966 through 2nd Summer 1967 (Item 30)
  - Registrar's Statistical, Spring 1967 thru 2nd Summer 1967 (Item 31)
  - Grade Distribution, Spring 1967, Fall 1967, Spring 1968 (Item 32)
  - Fall 1967 - 2nd Summer 1968 (Item 33)
  - Department Major Classification Report, Fall 1969 (Item 34)
  - Department Major Classification Report, Spring 1970 (Item 35)